# Dan Tran Front-end Web Developer

#### **CONTACT DETAILS**

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/dan -tran-b2b925226/

GitHub:

https://github.com/amia-real

**EMAIL:** 

danhuytran@gmail.com

#### **PROFILE**

Hi, I am Dan a front-end developer who specializes in React and JavaScript to make webpages come to life. To this end, I've developed a strong passion and drive to solve problems which will be instrumental to succeed in a web development position.

#### **SKILLS**

- HTML/CSS proficiency
- JavaScript/ jQuery / React /Firebase
- Python and Django Fundamentals
- Critical thinking
- Perform under Pressure
- Communication Skills
- Ability to Work in a Team
- Leadership Skills

#### **EDUCATION**

## Juno Web Development Bootcamp

October 2021 - December 2021

# University of Ottawa, Ottawa, bachelor's in biomedical sciences

August 2018 - May 2021

#### **CODING PROJECTS**

# Persona Messenger – Messenger App

JavaScript/HTML/CSS/React/Firebase Messenger application that allows real time messaging between users. Built using React while having all user data and chat information stored in firebase.

# Dynamic Depo – ecommerce site

JavaScript/HTML/SASS/Firebase/ Restful APIs Ecommerce site with functioning filtering of API data and firebase cart system. Site built using a restful API and vanilla JavaScript to accurately portray the functionality of an ecommerce app.

### Out Of Context – Movie and Gif API application

React/JavaScript/SCSS/HTML/Restful APIs React application that takes a movie title and through multiple API's returns 3 gifs relevant to said Movie. This app uses 3 consecutive API calls for each given movie and precise error handling for any possible scenario.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Vision mate - CNIB, Mississauga,

May 2020 – October 2020

Worked and connected with members of the visually impaired community which granted me a deeper understanding of their different needs and permitted me to interact accordingly.

# Organizer of CAIR radiology convention, Toronto,

June 2020 - June 2020

Worked to organize and help run a radiology convention within multiple team environments to bring an efficient experience to the participants and solve many high-pressure complications that happened to arise during the convention.